<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="0dp"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        app:layoutManager="androidx.recyclerview.widget.LinearLayoutManager"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent">

        <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content">

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/btn_Back"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginStart="@dimen/dp20"
                android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/dp20"
                android:src="@drawable/ic_baseline_close_24"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/tv_Title"
                android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/dp20"
                android:fontFamily="@font/mark_pro_medium"
                android:text="Description"
                android:textColor="@color/darkBlue"
                android:textSize="@dimen/sp16"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/tv_Description"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:layout_marginLeft="@dimen/dp20"
                android:layout_marginTop="@dimen/dp20"
                android:layout_marginRight="@dimen/dp20"
                android:fontFamily="@font/mark_pro_regular"
                android:gravity="left"
                android:paddingBottom="@dimen/dp20"
                android:text="Introducing Galaxy Note20 Ultra: The Power to Work. The Power to Play. This isn't the time to slow down, this is the time to forge ahead and take the opportunities that come your way. You don’t need a smartphone. You need a power phone. One as beautiful as it is intelligent with a pen that is mightier, a battery that doesn't leave you hanging and is as well-connected as you. Galaxy Note20 Ultra takes power to the next level with cutting-edge technology, letting you master whatever you choose to do next. Pen precision meets PC power with S Pen and Samsung Notes. So responsive, it feels like you're using a real pen to jot notes and sketch ideas. Then convert into Microsoft Word or PowerPoint, and save and sync across all your Galaxy devices while on the go. Send files to your friends wirelessly with Point to Share with other compatible Samsung devices. Simply select the pictures, videos or documents you want to share, then point your Galaxy Note20 Ultra 5G at your friend's device and tap Share. Intelligent Battery and Super Fast Charge learn from how you work and play to optimize battery life and boost your battery in minutes. Get the best Galaxy mobile gaming in the palm of your hand with its smooth gameplay experience and the adaptive Dynamic AMOLED 2X display. Get smooth motion, fluid scrolling and low blue light emissions on the 6.9' Infinity-O Display. HyperFast Processor transforms your working, gaming, and bingeing so you can multitask without slowing down. Operate from mobile to PC seamlessly with Link to Windows and share files with a simple drop and drag. Power on with Galaxy Note20 Ultra to take your mobile experience to the next level."
                android:textColor="@color/darkBlue"
                android:textSize="12sp"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@id/tv_Title" />

        </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>

    </androidx.core.widget.NestedScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>